We focus on the idea of ​​happiness a lot
The problem with this is that it takes our focus away from potentially more effective goals
It is better to seek meaning than happiness
12 Laws of Life About How to Live Right with Face
Subjugation, tragedy and malice
And one of the suggestions
In 12 Laws of Life
That the existence of life
Use it to classify it as an interaction between chaos and order, or the unknown and the known
You are always trying to balance these two things
If what you do is too familiar, then you are bored
Everything you do is so anonymous, you are anxious
And what you have to do is find a neutral line between these two
This broadens the meaning
If you can get these two things right then you will have your cake and eat it too
I hope people get the idea that there is a formula for existence
In the face of ill and conquering life
Noble and powerful
He is able to keep them at the worst possible times without making them disruptive or angry
12 Laws of Life, an antidote to chaos
Jordan B. Peterson
Available in all sales locations, digital and audiobooks